https://www.easygreen.com/privacy-policy/

CREATE AN ACCOUNT
FORGOT YOUR PASSWORD?
FORGOT YOUR DETAILS?
CONFIRM PASSWORD
ALREADY HAVE AN ACCOUNT?
HomePRIVACY POLICY
PRIVACY POLICY
Here’s how Easy Green Factory keeps and protects data our customers provide us:
Information Collection and Use
Easy Green Factory is the sole owner of information we collect on our website. We promise never to sell, share, or rent your personal information in any way differently from the ways we disclose in this policy. We collect information from our customers at several different points on our website.
Log Files
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ movements, and gather broad demographic information to help us serve our customers better. No personally identifiable information is linked to this process.
Links
Our website contains links to other sites. Please understand that EasyGreen® bears no responsibility for the privacy practices of sites we do not manage. We encourage you to exercise good judgment and to read the privacy policies of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement only applies to information collected by the EasyGreen® Factory website.
Security
EasyGreen® Factory takes every precaution to protect the information that site users submit. We protect the sensitive information you provide us both online and off-line.
If you have any questions about the security of our website, you may send an email to vinit.easygreen@gmail.com
Correcting/Updating Personal Information
If your personally identifiable information changes, (such as your zip code), or if you would prefer not to accept our occasional e-mails or newsletters, we will make every effort to correct, update, or remove the personal data provided to us. Updates, corrections, or removal from our customer list may be made by emailing our Customer Support department, sheetal1.easygreen@gmail.com.
Recent Posts
Healthy Habits For A Better Night’s Sleep
More than a third of American adults are not ge...
Lower Your Household Bills and Reduce Your Carbon Footprint
Americans spend 11% of their income on utility ...
Effective Ways To Reduce Food Waste
Americans discard 150,000 tons of usable produc...
Gardening Tricks to Save You Money
The number of Americans who love to garden has ...
How to Attract More Wildlife to Your Garden
With over 900 species of birds to see in North ...
For USA and CANADA:
